import '../models/question.dart';

final List<Question> questions = [
  Question(
    category: Category.sport,
    questionText:
        'Which team is currently the Women\'s Handball World Champion?',
    hint1: 'Hint1: This team is from Europe.',
    hint2:
        'Hint2: The country of this team is known for its baguettes and wine.',
    solution: 'Solution: France',
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.music,
    questionText: 'Who is the author of the hit song "Poker Face"?',
    hint1:
        'Hint1: This author, in addition to being a musician, has also made her debut as an actress.',
    hint2: 'Hint2: She is a 13-time Grammy Award winner.',
    solution: 'Solution: Lady Gaga',
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.movie,
    questionText:
        'What is the main character of the film titled "The Pianist"?',
    hint1: 'Hint1: The main character is played by Adam Brody.',
    hint2:
        'Hint2: The main character was a Polish-Jewish pianist, classical composer and Holocaust survivor.',
    solution: 'Solution: Władysław Szpilman',
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.animals,
    questionText: 'What animal is the largest mammal in the world?',
    hint1: 'Hint1: This animal lives in the oceans.',
    hint2: 'Hint2: This animal can reach a weight of up to 150 tons!',
    solution: 'Solution: The blue whale',
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.sport,
    questionText: 'Where will the 2028 Olympic Games take place?',
    hint1: 'Hint1: The city is located in the US state of California.',
    hint2: 'Hint2: The hallmark of this city is Hollywood.',
    solution: 'Solution: Los Angeles',
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.music,
    questionText: 'What is the name of the most popular female K-pop group?',
    hint1: 'Hint1: The team members are: Rose, Lisa, Jennie and Jisoo.',
    hint2:
        'Hint2: It is the only Korean group to perform as a headliner at the Coachella festival.',
    solution: 'Solution: BlackPink',
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.movie,
    questionText: 'What film won the Academy Award for Best Picture in 2023?',
    hint1: 'Hint1: The film\'s directors are Dan Kwan and Daniel Scheinert.',
    hint2:
        'Hint2: The film\'s main characters are played by Michelle Yeoh and Ke Huy Quan.',
    solution: 'Solution: Everything Everywhere All at Once',
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.animals,
    questionText: 'Where are penguins most numerous in the wild?',
    hint1: 'Hint1: It is the southernmost continent on Earth.',
    hint2:
        'Hint2: The lowest temperature ever recorded on Earth was recorded on this continent.',
    solution: 'Solution: Antarctica',
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.sport,
    questionText: 'How long is the quarter in American football?',
    hint1:
        'Hint1: The football quarter is slightly longer than in the NBA league.',
    hint2: 'Hint2: A football quarter lasts one-quarter of an hour.',
    solution: 'Solution: 15 minutes',
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.music,
    questionText:
        'In which town does the most famous electronic music festival Tomorrowland take place?',
    hint1: 'Hint1: This city is located in Belgium.',
    hint2:
        'Hint2: This city is located between three other big cities: Brussels, Antwerp and Ghent.',
    solution: 'Solution: Boom',
  ),
];
